Natalie Moran

11 Stephen Avenue, Rainham, Essex, RM13 7NP nataliemoran89@live.co.uk 07476706463 natmonlee.github.io/portfolio

Profile

Having been a healthcare professional for ten years, I am now looking to transition into the field of software development. I have enjoyed learning to code over the past year and a half, while also gaining valuable experiences by travelling extensively. I recently built a website that consumes an external API and displays response, then progressed to designing my own RESTful API. There are links to my personal projects on my portfolio website above. I am a passionate and enthusiastic learner, eager to build on my skills in a professional capacity.

Work History

Self-study J

June 2022 - Present

- Using online resources such as Codecademy Pro and freecodecamp
- Completing code challenges on Codecademy and Codewars
- Reading "Eloquent Javascript" by Marjin Haverbeke
- Developing a strong understanding of JavaScript; including promises, asynchronous programming, consuming third-party APIs and working with Node.js
- Writing semantic HTML
- Understanding responsive web design and utilising CSS layout models
- Gaining familiarity with VS Code and command line tools such as Git, Bash, and npm

Brockwell Park Surgery Care Coordinator (Feb 2021 – June 2022)

November 2019 – June 2022

- Internal promotion after just over a year working at the surgery
- Ran regular searches using the clinical system and exported data to Excel
- Utilised various software to send batch text-messages, refer patients and generate forms and correspondence
- Ensured and tracked appropriate follow-up for patients, focusing particularly on vulnerable groups
- Filed results and documents, adding codes to patient records as required
- Took on additional role as COVID lead during the pandemic, handling all queries, liaising with vaccination centres and organising immunisation of housebound patients
- Assisted in creating work instructions, procedures and training materials
- Contributed to meetings discussing targets and strategies

Receptionist (November 2019 - February 2021)

- The only full-time reception staff member, at times managing independently during the height of the pandemic
- Managed surgery telephone, triaged patients, scheduled appointments, requested prescriptions and registered new patients
- Organised surgery email inbox and handled queries on our website
- Evaluated efficiency of new website by assessing its effect on phone and email enquiries

King's College Hospital Healthcare Assistant

June 2018 - November 2019

- Delivered care to patients on the cardiology ward and intensive care unit
- Provided close supervision to more vulnerable patients when required
- Monitored patient health using hospital equipment and accurately recorded findings on the clinical system
- Maintained enthusiasm and composure during long shifts, challenging work and emergency situations

David Lewis Pharmacy July 2012 - January 2018 Dispensary Assistant (April 2015 - January 2018)

- Progressed to dispensary after completing relevant qualifications
- Dispensed medication and processed prescriptions on the clinical system
- Accurately filed, counted and recorded prescriptions for monthly submission
- Managed schedule of regular deliveries to patients
- Maintained stock levels and placed monthly bulk orders based on current usage of products

Counter Assistant (July 2012 - April 2015)

- Operated the till and reconciled cash on a weekly basis
- Independently liaised with suppliers and made decisions on which stock to purchase
- Provided medical advice on topics such as healthy living, smoking cessation and sexual health

Nursing Homes UK Administrator

January - April 2012

- Updated the company website using a content management system
- Verified and updated information in Excel spreadsheets
- Created basic advertisements for clients using text and images

Qualifications

Bath Spa University

September 2007-June 2010

Diploma in English Literature and Creative Writing

Hobbies

Include running, scuba diving and PC and board games.